Thank You, Daddy
Maraud. Merde.
Did you see everything?
Yeah.
I see.
I broke my promise to Kuma.
One more regret.
Marauders.
I'm sorry! Dr.
Megimonose,
Here, give me your hand. What for?
Kuma entrusted this to me.
It's a little present
for your 10th birthday.
Wait, it's from Dad? Really?
There you go.
A sapphire?
It's so pretty!
It looks like the sun!
Oh, I love it so much!
So that's what it is. Yep.
Like the sun god!
Kuma just said it was a good luck charm.
Who could have imagined?
Kuma saw promise in
that boy two years ago,
and now he's turned into
something like this.
Speaking of, is it true Straw Hat
is my dad's best friend's son? Yes.
I was surprised when you
two arrived here together.
Fate can work in mysterious ways.
You've been in that room
for a while, you know.
You've missed out on quite a number
of happenings here on Egghead.
For example, Straw Hat Luffy and his
crew just saved me from a deadly pinch.
I'll get you up to speed.
Then we'll join them
once you've rested a bit.
I truly am sorry, Bunny.
I'm just a paltry hired hand, after all.
No.
No!
This isn't your fault!
It's his!
Present Day
Egghead, New World
Damn it!
I can't move at all!
What the hell did he do?
Honey!
How are we going to get out of this?
I don't know.
I've never seen this power.
Hungry food.
Meat.
Somebody get me meat.
I'm begging you.
I wish I could, but I can't move.
Reporting in.
Vegapunk's bodyguard,
Sentomaru, has been captured.
Sentomaru.
Bonnie.
Listen to me, pirate jewelry, Bonnie.
Your father, Bartholomew Kuma,
is dead.
What's going on in there?
No one below the rank of Commodore
can enter, so we don't know.
Have you seen today's news?
Apparently, the new Emperor of
the Sea just took a hostage.
Um, well, it's quite the bold move.
I'd wager some bloodshed is inevitable.
It says the Navy sent more
battleships than they sent to Ohara.
Seems excessive.
I sure hope Dr.
Straw Hats' Hostage Situation
Vegapunk is alright
You've got it all wrong.
Watch you silly billies!
Keep your hands up like this.
And kablam!
There, you get it?
You're amazing.
One more time, I want to see it again!
No, I can't see it out of my pants.
You greedy boys and girls!
You're insatiable.
Is something wrong, dragon?
If Kuma is being driven by a
fragment of his remaining psyche.
If you were him, where would you go, Eva?
Huh?
I'd march my cyborg butt straight
to Marie Joie and open fire.
But Kuma isn't like that.
It just leaves.
But not to worry.
It's time to join your
father in the afterlife.
Fine!
Then go ahead!
But you're coming with me!
Distorted future!
Nika, like...
Nika? Future!
What is this?
I got weaker again.
Why?
Of course.
You are that fool's child.
But that is all you know, a name.
You have no idea what it is.
You know nothing.
What the hell are you
talking about, old man?
It seems she truly is crudous.
She hasn't made the connection
between Nika and Straw Hat.
What a pity.
What are you doing?
Who gave Straw Hat all of that food?
Not us, sir.
We didn't give him anything, I swear.
Cuff him with Sea Prism Stone at once.
Of course, right away.
Yes, sir.
Stop right there!
Go away!
What's happening?
I can't change his age.
But why?
You seem to be wondering
why your strength is waning.
Why?
Do you know where your power came from?
It was given to you.
By me.
What?
It was an experiment.
You were given a Devil Fruit extract.
I wondered if an infant who could not
eat solid food could be granted power.
But the AJ's fruit is useless.
It allows you to transform into any
possible future version of yourself,
but as you learn
to face reality, you begin to see
that your potential is quite narrow.
You want to believe that
Nika is real, don't you?
Nika is real!
I've been searching for him ever
since you took my dad from me!
I knew if I found him, he'd
have the power to set dad free!
And yet, your weakening power is proof
that your faith in Nika is ebbing.
Your father also believed in
that foolish buccaneer legend.
I remember what he said
to me many years ago.
I want to be like Nika and
protect people from suffering.
Before she died, your mother was the
eighth wife of someone from the Holy Land,
and I conducted drug experiments on her.
But they were a failure, and
those blue blemishes appeared.
Disappointment aside, it was interesting
that her child inherited the side effects.
Hey, I think something fell from the sky.
It was you.
It was all you.
That's what happened to her.
It was your experiment!
The sapphire scales took
Kuma's family apart!
He sacrificed himself to save
his daughter from that sickness,
and you acted like your deal
was a favor to him! Oh, no.
You failed to see this
from my perspective.
Tell me, Doctor, do you concern yourself
with the feelings of mere insects?
I should think not.
Is that a pacifista? No.
Look closer.
He has paw pads on his hands.
It can't be!
It's the real Kuma!
This is an emergency!
I'm on the southwestern shore!
And the former warlord of the sea,
Bartholomew Kuma, has appeared!
He's advancing towards
the island's center!
The authority chip isn't working!
I have no way to stop it now!
Kuma's here? But bye!
What are you going on about, Kuma?
That's impossible.
I can't do it.
I'm too afraid.
I can't say a word.
Stop him!
Open fire now! Yes, sir!
Hey, Dad.
I feel like I'm falling apart.
Maybe.
Maybe it would be easier
if I gave up and died right now.
I'm sorry. Dad!
This is insufferable.
Silence, you noisy brat.
Shoot her in the head.
Stop it!
I'm sorry, Dad.
You worked so hard to save my life.
Oh, my God. Dad!
Daddy!
Put all of you, Kuma!
I'm impossible.
Why is this happening, Vegapunk?
What did you do?
This is absurd.
He's supposed to be dead.
Listen to me, buccaneer boy.
You will live as a
slave, then you will die.
That is your lot in life.
Your mother's in heaven now.
But you know, it's better this way.
Kumachi, I'm so happy!
I'm sorry, Kumachi, but
I'm going to die soon.
Why is he still alive?
I killed him when the
revolutionaries took him.
He should have self-destructed already!
I pressed the switch myself!
C-Saturn, no!
Curse you!
The city.
Hey, what now? Do we stay put?
Did Kuma do all that?
He's done it now!
He backed one of the five elders!
What? No!
They're the highest
authority in the world!
He's lost his mind!
A slave just struck an elder.
This can't be happening!
It's completely unheard of!
Rescue Saint Saturn!
He's buried under the collapsed buildings!
I can move!
Hey, me too!
All thanks to Kuma, huh?
Hey, Bonnie! You okay?
It's no time to lose!
Grab Bonnie and we can
head up to the sunning!
We don't have to win this fight!
We just have to get away!
I'll grab Comane, take him with us!
Wait a sec!
I don't know what happened.
I never installed that
self-destruct switch in you.
I feared that if I turned you into a bomb,
that the government would be tempted
to use you as a suicide weapon.
But I could only disobey them so much,
so I decided to install a
total shutdown switch instead.
Now that it has been pressed, you
should be in a vegetative state.
You shouldn't be able to respond to
commands, let alone act on your own.
If you don't possess
reason, what can you act on?
What drove you to Bonnie's side?
Science cannot explain it.
It's illogical.
So the tales must be true, then.
It's not their physical strength
that makes Buccaneer people special.
At one point in time, they...
That's it.
It's over now.
Kuma.
Any luck here?
No, Straw Hat just vanished on us.
What do we tell HQ?
Thank you, Dad, for everything.
I saw your memories.
I saw your whole life.
And you know, you weren't
the only one I saw.
I saw Mom.
I'm so happy. I love her.
She was the best.
And thank you for writing
me so many letters.
Reading those words made me so happy.
It's not fair.
Everybody says that you're a tyrant.
But I know you're the nicest person ever.
And the coolest.
I have the best dad in the world.
Believe me.
I'll never forget it.
He's coming back!
Dammit, this is bad!
One punch ain't taking him out!
Speak, Vegapunk.
What is your explanation for this?
Was it your doing?
Well, I suppose it must look that way.
You could say it was the
power of love, if you like.
Very well, then.
Call it one of humanity's delusions.
An error in their construction.
Hey, what just happened?
It looks like he's regenerating.
Farewell.
I have no more use for you.
Get away, Dad!
Get out of there!
Leave Bonnie alone, you spider geezer!
Get the hell out of here!
Come with us, our asses!
We got a debt to repay!
Ready to go?
You were right.
You aren't the same crew I faced before.
I've gone back to hell already!
Why don't you show me? Franky!
How much you've implied!
VEGAPUNK! My dad isn't moving! Kuma?
WHAT DO WE DO?
Atlas, carry him to the Lobby phase!
EASY Pass, I GOT THIS!
QUICKLY, Atlas!
LEAVE THIS ONE TO ME!
TAKE CARE OF Brain AND KUMA!
We're just gonna let him escape.
I don't care.
This is a mess.
Now we've got Kuma here too.
That's too many big
shots all in one place.
Better get this over with quick.
Now you can't take the pressure?
What a sad man you've become,
Kizaru. That's not Borsalino I knew.
I am pathetic, aren't I?
If I'd known today would be like this, I
would have wanted a darker pair of shades.
This is an order.
Eliminate all enemies of the government.
Let none of them remain.
Prepare all ships for the Buster Call!
This island has been designated as
a threat to the world government.
All units, prepare for bombardment!
In the name of justice, we'll
burn it all to the ground!
Spare no effort!
Show no mercy!
Open fire and leave nothing behind!
Fate!
Deadly's a master call!
Those who study the forbidden
secrets of the world.
Those who carry traitor's blood.
Those who awaken the
might of an ancient god.
All inconveniences,
all must be eradicated.
Conquering the world, believing in the future
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
What did you see, what did you learn?
nani o mite nani o shitte
Once again, I couldn't save a soul
mata daremo mamorenai no
My fault their voices're fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
Don't even have time to hang my head
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
We're setting off again, my ship!
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the open skies
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
Which is why...
bokura wa
Everyday, we can't quit
EVERYDAY owarenai
Everyday, we can't lose
EVERYDAY makerenai
We've got something right here to defend
mamoru mono ga koko ni wa aru
Were my predictions all wrong?
yosou chigai kamo
But I can't stop anymore
tomarenai yo mou
We forge on, sharing the loneliness
kodoku o ima wakeai susumu
Don't chicken out now
ojikezukuna yo
I'm nothing like I used to be
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare ni mo jama dekinai yo
So move!
saa doite
Conquering the world, believing in the future,
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
counting the endless nights
ikutsumo no yoru kazoete
What did you see, what did you learn,
nani o mite nani o shitte
to realize what's really important?
taisetsu na koto ni kizuita no